# Sara Kuuipo Mishina Kunz

# **UX/UI** Designer

#### CONTACT

- 240 575 0889
- sara@sarakunz.com
- 🕜 Greater Boston, MA
- www.behance.net/ sarakunz
- in www.linkedin.com/ in/sara-kunz-UX-UI

#### **SKILLS**

- UI Design
- UX Research
- User Personas
- Wireframing
- Usability Testing
- Prototyping
- Mock-ups
- Branding
- Style Guidelines
- Sketch App
- inVision

### **EDUCATION**

- Front End Development Certificate
   Career Foundry
   2020 -in progress
- UI Design Certificate
  Career Foundry
  2020
- Bachelors, Fine Arts University of Oregon 2007-2012

#### **PROFILE**

UI/UX Designer excelling in unique user-based solutions with smooth design. Experienced in content creation, collaborating between clients and users, and crafting fantastic stylistic guidelines. Skilled in wireframing, presentation mockups, storytelling, prototyping, user personas, and style guides.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Board Member: Design + Branding

#### 2020

#### Simply Circus, Newton MA

Synthesize business and customer needs to create cohesive and beautiful brand guidelines for a non-profit circus school.

- Rebranding with a focus on user/client research and establishing style and brand guidelines
- Communicate design choices to board members and contribute to team meetings.

## Performing Artist, Sole Proprietor

2013-2020

#### Flyin' Hawaiian Productions, Global

Running a one-woman-show (literally) that toured in 20+ countries, with a specialization in comedy and circus arts.

- Created, tested, and performed award-winning and critically acclaimed plays, stories, and comedy
- Managed all contracts, finances, branding, collaborations, and media for The Flyin' Hawaiian Show and other performances
  - Excelled in continuous learning to develop products

#### Artist + Instructor

2017-2019 (seasonal)

#### Muse Paintbar, Somerville MA

Providing clear step-by-step painting instructions in a performative setting to give first-time artists an immersive and entertaining evening of art.

- Design and replicate all Master Paintings
- Breakdown and teach the painting process (acrylic)
- Improvise, engage, and entertain parties of 10-50

# Sara Kuuipo Mishina Kunz

# **UX/UI** Designer

#### CONTACT

- 240 575 0889
- sara@sarakunz.com
- 0

#### **SKILLS**

- UI Design
- UX Research
- User Personas
- Wireframing
- Usability Testing
- Prototyping
- Mock-ups
- Branding
- Style Guidelines
- Sketch App
- inVision

#### **EDUCATION**

- Front End Development Certificate
   Career Foundry
   2020 -in progress
- UI Design Certificate
  Career Foundry
  2020
- Bachelors, Fine Arts University of Oregon 2007-2012

#### **PROFILE**

UI/UX Designer excelling in unique user-based solutions with smooth design. Experienced in content creation, collaborating between clients and users, and crafting fantastic stylistic guidelines. Skilled in wireframing, presentation mockups, storytelling, prototyping, user personas, and style guides.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Sara Kuuipo Mishina Kunz

# **UX/UI** Designer

#### CONTACT

- 240 575 0889
- 🕢 sara@sarakunz.com
- Greater Boston, MA
- saramishina.com
- in linkedin.com/in/ sara-kunz-UX-UI

#### **SKILLS**

- UI Design
- UX Research
- User Personas
- Wireframing
- Usability Testing
- Prototyping
- Mock-ups
- Branding
- Style Guidelines
- Sketch App
- inVision

### **EDUCATION**

- Front End Development Certificate
   Career Foundry
   2020
- UI Design Certificate
  Career Foundry
  2020
- Bachelors, Fine Arts University of Oregon 2007-2012

#### **PROFILE**

UI/UX Designer excelling in unique user-based solutions with smooth design. Experienced in content creation, collaborating between clients and users, and crafting fantastic stylistic guidelines. Skilled in wireframing, presentation mockups, storytelling, prototyping, user personas, and style guides.

## **UX PROJECTS**

Founder +UX UI Designer

2018-current

#### Survivor Stories, Boston MA

Develop an app for sexual assault survivors that provides evidence based coping mechanisms

- Lead and synthesixe user research into app structure
- Execute all stages of design from sketches to final screens
- Use Lean and Agile methods to develop product
- Lead all funding initiatives and presentations

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Board Member: Design + Branding

2020

#### Simply Circus, Newton MA

Synthesize business and customer needs to create cohesive and beautiful brand guidelines for a non-profit circus school.

- Rebranding with a focus on user/client research and establishing style and brand guidelines
- Communicate design choices to board members and contribute to team meetings.

### Performing Artist, Sole Proprietor

2013-2020

#### Flyin' Hawaiian Productions, Global

Running a one-woman-show (literally) that toured in 20+ countries, with a specialization in comedy and circus arts.

- Created, tested, and performed award-winning and critically acclaimed plays, stories, and comedy
- Managed all contracts, finances, branding, collaborations, and media for The Flyin' Hawaiian Show and other performances
  - Excelled in continuous learning to develop products